(Past Sheldon:)No. But your ability to
perceive their existence is conditional...
(Past Leonard:)-There's three?
-Each more daunting than the last.
(Past Sheldon:)-Have a seat.
-Okay.
No, that's where I sit.
(Past Leonard:)What's the difference?
(Past Sheldon:)This seat is ideally located...
(Past Sheldon:)...in relation to the heat source in the
winter and a cross breeze in the summer.
(Past Sheldon:)It also faces the television
at a direct angle...
(Past Sheldon:)...allowing me to immerse myself
in entertainment or game play...
(Past Sheldon:)...without being subjected to conversation.
As a result...
(Past Sheldon:)...I've placed it in a state of eternal dibs.
(Past Leonard:)Can you do that?
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
That's Latin for "My chair my rules."
(Past Sheldon:)Now, you said on the phone
that your area of study is physics.